{
    "subject": "Maija_DiGiorgio",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Bitter_Jester",
    "human_readable": "Maija DiGiorgio directed the film Bitter Jester.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9143812656402588,
            "question": "Who directed the film Bitter Jester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8413304686546326,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Maija DiGiorgio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7523968815803528,
            "question": "What other films has Maija DiGiorgio directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6397721767425537,
            "question": "What is the plot of Bitter Jester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6302640438079834,
            "question": "Is Bitter Jester a fictional or documentary film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5757876038551331,
            "question": "Where was Bitter Jester filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5711509585380554,
            "question": "Are there any actors known to have starred in Bitter Jester?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48217716813087463,
            "question": "What year was Bitter Jester released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.383743017911911,
            "question": "What genre is Bitter Jester likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27461129426956177,
            "question": "Has Bitter Jester won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maija DiGiorgio directed the film Bitter Jester.",
            "html": "yago_31284_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Bitter Jester likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_31284_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Bitter Jester released?",
            "html": "yago_31284_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any actors known to have starred in Bitter Jester?",
            "html": "yago_31284_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31284_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because according to the documents, Maija DiGiorgio not only directed the film Bitter Jester, but also starred in it and received rave reviews for her work on the documentary."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Maija DiGiorgio is the director of the film \"Bitter Jester,\" as evidenced by multiple references to her as the writer, director, and editor of the documentary."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}